kaleidoscope.co.uk 2012-05-11

# Buy Ladies Clothes | Ladies Dresses and Clothes Online | Kaleidoscope

What Is Your Privacy Policy?

We respect your privacy, and promise to use any information we hold about you in a safe and responsible way. By shopping with us, you are agreeing to our Privacy Policy, in particular, our use of your information, as outlined below. We control information we have collected about you that is relevant to your account. This includes: 

•Your credit history 

•The credit histories of any people you are financially linked to 

•Your purchasing habits with us 

•To verify your identity and that you are least 18 years of age (we cannot sell any goods to you if you are below 18 years of age).

We will use your information in the following ways:

**Reference checks**

When you open an account with us we will need to check your credit history and store the search on file. We will re-run checks each time you apply for, or we offer you further credit.

**Marketing**

We may contact you with promotions we think might interest you, as part of our market research, either by mail, telephone or email.

**Third Party Marketing**

We may share your details to third parties whose offers we think might interest you.

**Training**

We randomly monitor calls made to our Customer Services for training. This information will not be used for any other purpose.

**Important**

By ordering from us you are consenting to us sharing your information with other organisations and to us or them contacting you for the marketing purposes by mail, telephone, e-mail or otherwise. If you do not wish to be contacted by us by telephone for marketing purposes, or if you do not wish to be contacted by other organisations for marketing purposes, please tell us.

Please write to us at: Kaleidoscope, Ingleby Road, Bradford BD99 2XG.

We may also pass information about you to agents, service providers and employees to carry out services. In the course of providing such services, we may transfer your personal information outside the European Economic Area. We will employ appropriate security measures to proetect your personal information where this is the case. 

Any information we collect about customers' browsing and buying habits is used to improve the Kaleidoscope website and the products and services offered to our customers. It also assists us with the detection and prevention of fraud.

We will collect information from you when opening your account and processing your orders. 

We will automatically collect information such as your browser IP address to make shopping with us easier, for example, remembering your log-in details. 

We will use cookies (electronic tags) to monitor your browsing and buying habits on our site, for example, which pages are visited, and whether they are purchased from. 

Information we hold about you is securely stored electronically. When you open an account with us, your details are encrypted, and remain so every time you purchase from us. Personal information is encrypted to protect against fraud. 

Callers to our Customer Services will be subject to a security check.

Online customers will require a log-in and password to access their account. 

Our courier service will have selected access to your details for delivery purposes only.

**Third party advertising**

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on our behalf. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. 

Currently we have relationships with the following third-party ad networks:  

Criteo places cookies on the browsers of visitors to its website(s) and may send its own cookies to the visitors’ cookie file. The cookies will allow Criteo to apply its Personalized Retargeting technology and to serve Personalized banners.

Criteo only employs anonymous cookies for Personalized banners, the Cookie is a means by which information relating to internet activity is recorded.

Criteo will collect and use this data in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations (including but not limited to laws governing privacy, and data protection).

The data collected and used by Criteo is at its sole discretion will only contain non-personal data. This data will be anonymous and will not contain the name, address, telephone number, email address or IP address of the Visitors.

Criteo’s Privacy Policy will be available at the following address:  

Criteo’s Privacy Policy includes information for users on how to opt-out or being cookie retargeted.

**Customer Reviews**

When you submit a customer review, we request a nickname and a location (optional. These details are published alongside the reviews on the website.
